[
    {
      "question": " Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges?",
      "correct_answer": "Narmada",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mahanadi",
        "Son",
        "Netravati"
      ]
    },
    {
   
      "question": "2. The Central Rice Research Station is situated in",
      "correct_answer": "Cuttack",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chennai",
        "Banglore",
        "Mumbai"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is?",
      "correct_answer": "Silver",
      "incorrect_answers": ["zinc", "Copper", "Gold"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one of the following rivers originates in Brahmagiri range of Western Ghats?",
      "correct_answer": "Cauvery",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tapti",
        "Krishna",
        "Yamuna"
      ]
    },
    {
      
      "question": "The country that has the highest in Barley Production?",
      "correct_answer": "Russia",
      "incorrect_answers": ["India", "China", "Germany"]
    },
    {

      "question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Kingston",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Rio%20de%20Janeiro", "Dar%20es%20Salaam", "Kano"]
    },
    {
      "question": "23. Which of the following is not a nuclear power center?",
      "correct_answer": "Chamera",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kakrapara", "Kota", "Narora"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "FFC stands for",
      "correct_answer": "Film Finance Corporation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Federation of Football Council",
        "Foreign Finance Corporation",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "question": "Which is the country which has the Great Barrier Reef?",
      "correct_answer": "Australia",
      "incorrect_answers": ["England", " New Zealand", "Ireland"]
    }
  ]
  